(Mrs Cooper:)I am not abandoning you.
(Mrs Cooper:)Sheldon, abandoning you is leaving you
in a basket on a church doorstep.
(Mrs Cooper:)I am going to Hollywood
and thank a wax Ronald Reagan...
(Mrs Cooper:)...for his service to our country.
(Sheldon:)We appear to be at a crossroads
in our relationship, Mother.
- Well, I guess we are.
- Sorry. Syrup.
(Sheldon:)All right, Mom. When you're at
the Ripley's Believe It Or Not Museum...
(Sheldon:)...if they have an exhibit about a mother
who threw away a chance...
...to spend a day with the world's
most wonderful son, believe it, it's true.
(Leonard:)I hadn't...
(Sheldon:)That lecture was a waste of time.
(Sheldon:)I made more accurate diagrams
of the expansion of the early universe...
(Sheldon:)...on the nursery wall
with the contents of my diaper.
(Amy:)Are you getting sick?
(Sheldon:)No, I'm just allergic to people who get
Nobel Prizes for no good reason.
(Amy:)Sheldon, is it possible
that your foul mood or...